[
{
"question":"Best Player for the season 14/15",
"answers":["Alexis Sanchez","Harry Kane","Eden Hazard","KDB"],
"correctAnswer": "Eden Hazard"},
{
"question":"Winners of the season 15/16",
"answers":["Arsenal","Spurs","Chelsea","leicester city"],
"correctAnswer": "leicester city"},
{
"question":"Best Coach of Serie A in 17/18 season",
"answers":["Maurizio Sarri","Massimillano Allegri","Antonio Conte","A.Ventura"],
"correctAnswer": "Maurizio Sarri"},
{
"question":"Best Keeper of the World Cup",
"answers":["Thibaut Courtois","Kepa Arrizabalaga","Jordan Pickford","Subasic"],
"correctAnswer":"Thibaut Courtois"},
{
"question":"Chelsea's new manager for 18/19 season",
"answers":["A","Maurizio Sarri","C","D"],
"correctAnswer": "Maurizio Sarri"},
{
"question":"Best Coach",
"answers":["Maurizio Sarri","B","C","D"],
"correctAnswer": "Maurizio Sarri"},
{
"question":"Best Coach",
"answers":["Maurizio Sarri","B","C","D"],
"correctAnswer": "Maurizio Sarri"},
{
"question":"Best Coach",
"answers":["Maurizio Sarri","B","C","D"],
"correctAnswer": "Maurizio Sarri"},
{
"question":"Best Coach",
"answers":["Maurizio Sarri","B","C","D"],
"correctAnswer": "Maurizio Sarri"},
{
"question":"Best Coach",
"answers":["Maurizio Sarri","B","C","D"],
"correctAnswer": "Maurizio Sarri"}
]